{
    "id": "030b1705e6dc4b00b75dc2db90cacafc",
    "title": "Simple Past And Past Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The patient .................................... before the doctor arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "has died",
                "had died"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f59d35fa6f9f4ea6a741a2b2e7880be8"
        },
        {
            "question": "As the fire broke out, people ................................. out of their house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hurried",
                "has hurried",
                "had hurried"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4be62ef171094faeba860bb18770fe73"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... him yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "meet",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "39b2ba4493d84b73a008b2fd365be48c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I recognized him immediately as I ................................. him before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "have seen",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d8d69a79017f4496a8583ce7dbcf04a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I .................................. with my friend during his last days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stayed",
                "would stay",
                "had stayed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "83882476130b44aabd5770179b74fd57"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he ................................ in time, he would have got the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "applied",
                "has applied",
                "had applied"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "66f7d220138144b395ac55a77d459e1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "By the time the firemen arrived, the fire ................................ many huts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "destroyed",
                "was destroying",
                "had destroyed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "833ccaf17370479c81af5c6962c1eb81"
        },
        {
            "question": "Long before the chief guest arrived, the invitees ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "assembled",
                "have assembled",
                "had assembled"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "26c66dc129b34bf3980783cc41097c28"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I .................................. my application in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sent",
                "have sent",
                "had sent"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6da2c8e2b6e143b78b6e2e992dc255be"
        },
        {
            "question": "I did not speak to him, as I ....................................... been introduced to him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was not",
                "had not",
                "has not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "632ebc4fc0994de886be3f4f0e296f9e"
        }
    ]
}